First of all, if we talk about the market, then today there was a
wide opening in Nifty,
after that
Mirwaiz
and Nifty saw a rise of 184 percent today
and in this video we will talk
about those people
and the company's market back stock of 62000 300
crores is of important
importance and the company is divided
and here you can see the performance of the company, the
company's net worth is 1.50 crores
and now if we talk about the positive points in the company, then the
company has reduced its debt and the
company is almost debt free and the profit of the last 15
years is
2375 crores and the dividend payout of the company is 2133 crores
and the placement of deposits is
1.049 crores,
1194 crores, 1473 crores,
1304 crores
and if we talk about share holding and the
holding of proper motor is 4805 crores, sanitation
building
28-12-13 crores and public holding is
276 crores
And now if we talk about the company's side, then today a
rise of four percent has been seen in the city
and at this time
Servi and Share Mubarak have the support of ₹100
and at this time RSS sticker RS
is in the exam and this share is
subscribed and at this time discount is available,
if you want to buy in this company then you
can subscribe for 12, that's all in this video, if you
like and share the video mentioned in the video
and subscribe to our channel.